Roxana Leoveanu

9/6 Professor Ciortea Street, Cluj-Napoca roxana.veronica.leoveanu@gmail.com +40 0744939558

Career profile

Self-motivated and enthusiastic worker with experience in different fields, marketing area and IT environment. Confident, hard-working, and committed to seeing results in the appointed position. Reliable and dedicated to finding a place that will benefit from my superior skill set and energetic drive.

Education

Front-end Web Development - Participation Diploma The Informal School of IT Cluj-Napoca, Cluj County

Graduated 02/2018

- Web Introduction (Client-Server architectures, TCP/IP Protocol, HTTP Protocol)
- HTML (Basics, Elements, Attributes, Tables, Form Elements)
- CSS (Syntax, Base Rules, Positioning and Layout, Pseudo-class and Pseudo-elements, RESPONSIVE Web Design)
- DOM (methods, document, elements, html, css, events, nodes, navigation)
- JAVASCRIPT (Functions, Scope, Exceptions, Events, Objects JS, Methods, Prototypes, JS BOM)
- JSON (syntax, types, objects, arrays, parse, stringify, JSON)
- JQUERY Basics
- AJAX (XML Http Request, response, promises)
- OOP basics about classes, objects and inheritance
- ES6 concepts and basic principles
- GIT: learned the principles and basic commands
- REACT JS basic
 - ➤ Intro in IT Participation Diploma The Informal School of IT • Cluj-Napoca, Cluj

Graduated 08/2017

- Basic OOP concepts & programming languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Basic database concepts: SQL language Windows Desktop Apps, testing tools
- Programming fundamentals (OS, programing languages, technologies, devices)
- Client-Server Technology, testing tools
- Web Browsers, testing tools
- Mobile platforms, testing tools
- Software product lifecycle
- Agile/Scrum/ Waterfall, V-Model methodology

Bachelor's degree Babes Bolyai Cluj-Napoca University, Faculty of Economic Sciences and Business Administration, Specialization Economics of Commerce, Tourism and Services -Tourism and services Cluj-Napoca, Cluj County

Graduated 07/2008

Employment History

Marketing SpecialistNapoca Imobiliare, Cluj-Napoca

07/2019 - 02/2020

- Provide guidance and assist sellers and buyers in marketing and purchasing property for the right price under the best terms
- Determine client needs and financials abilities to propose the best solutions that suit them
- Intermediate negotiation processes, consult clients on market conditions, prices, mortgages, legal requirements and related matters, ensuring a fair and honest dealing
- Perform comparative market analysis to estimate properties value
- Prepare necessary paperwork (contracts, leases, deeds, closing statements)
- Maintain and update listings of available properties
- Develop networks and cooperate with attorneys, mortgage lenders and contractors
- Promote sales through advertisements, open houses and listing services
- Follow the efficiency of the company's means of promotion and propose new means and methods of promotion
- Remain knowledgeable about real estate markets and best practices
 - Procurement expertProxpert Consulting, Cluj-Napoca

09/2017 - 06/2019

- Knowledge of legislation in the field of public procurement
- Experience in drawing up procurement documentation for beneficiaries (public or private)
- Experience in monitoring the progress of the acquisitions within the deadlines established between the parties
- Experience in purchase planning
- Experience in budgeting offers

Marketing SpecialistEXIMTUR SRL, Cluj-Napoca, Cluj

06/2013 - 09/2017

- Developing strategy to approach and attract new corporate clients, prospecting Market at national level, negotiation of contracts
- Maintaining the relations with company clients within the department, and concluding collaboration contracts with them; travel reports drafting, periodical analyses of traffic and costs in favor of the client corporation
- Analysis of sales evolution, monthly and annual reports
- Representing the company at business events, fairs and exhibitions
- Organization of events (courses, groups, team building, organization of Fairs, corporate events) for corporate clients and for the company
- Registration for the participants in the courses of the School of Tourism within the company
- Providing our clients with the best travel package deals
- Assist clients with reservations, transfers and changes
- Tracking public procurement legislation
- Signing contracts, for air transport and accommodation services, within the Marketing Department by following the public procurement procedures
- Preparing all the documents needed for offers and bids

Economist REMARUL 16 FEBRUARIE SA Cluj-Napoca, Cluj County

11/2009 - 05/2013

- Accounting and registration statements
- Accounting and record cash register in RON and foreign currency, recording payments and collections
- Preparing invoices for customers and expedition documents
- Tracking of the payments

Technical skills

- HTML5
- CSS

- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap

Skills and abilities

- Results driven
- Fast learning
- Attention to details
- Analytical mindset
- Time management
- Self- motivated
- Teamwork
- Conflict resolution

Languages

- Romanian native
- English Proficient
- Italian Conversational

References

Radu Nicolae Hriniuc - Sales Manager EXIMTUR SRL +40 751010926 radu.hriniuc@eximtur.ro